Ke Li

Fullstack Web Developer

X

sr.frontenddev210@gmail.com

- **** +86 187 4150 9250
- **S** Skype: live:rjh951006_1
- ? TianJin, China in Linkedin
 - Github HackRank

PROFILE

My name is Ke Li and I am a passionate full-stack developer with extensive knowledge and experience.

Since 2010 I have been focusing on advanced web and cross-platform mobile development.

During the freelance work so far, I've acquired modern cutting-edge technologies, the best practices, and a solid background in network/security and became a strong problem solver, fast learner.

I always look for a great team for the next challenges, always aspiring to work with great, potential partners!

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree, Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications Yonsei University 2008 – 2012

SKILLS

ES6+, Babel, Webpack, Gulp, Airbnb JS style, JQuery, ESLint, Prettier,
Node.js Express.js, Nest.js, Fastify, Koa, Restify, Jest, Mocha/Chai, Prisma, TypeORM, Sequelize, Mongoose, Knex, AWS Appsync
Typescript
PHP Laravel, Lumen, Codelgniter, Yii2, PHPUnit, Doctrine
Python Django, Flask, Web Scraping
Angular Version 9+ with Ivy rendering engine, NgRX, NgXS, RxJS, Jamine/Karma, Angular Universal, Angular Material, Kendo UI, DevExtreme
React.js Redux, Next.js, GatsbyJS, Hooks API, React testing library, Jest, Jest, Mocha/Chai, Storybook
Vue.js Version 3 with Vuex, Nuxt.js, Jest, Mocha/Chai
Git Bitbucket, Github, Gitlab, large-scale repo owner experience for 2 years,
Messaging, Queue Techniques RabbitMQ, Apache Kafka, MQTT
REST API development Stateless API design, Swagger, Postman
GraphQL Apollo, Prisma, Voyager, Urql, AWS Amplify Client, Relay
Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis, Sqlite, MsSQL
AWS EC2, Lambda, S3, CloudFormation, Appsync, Cognito, Amplify
DevOps, CI/CD Docker, Docker-Compose, Terraform, Ansible, Kubernetes, Circle CI, Bitbucket Pipeline, Jenkins, Travis CI, Github Action, Gitlab CI, AWS Cloudformation
Server administration Ubuntu, CentOS, AWS EC2, CPanel, SSH, Shell scripts, Networking, Nginx, Apache
Network / Security Standards

OAuth, JWT, SSO, SSL, CORS, RESTful, SOAP, RPC, DNS, HTTP/s

LANGUAGES

English

• • • •

Korean

• • • • •

Chinese



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Datategy 2

Fullstack Developer / Lead developer (Remote freelance)

03/2019 - 07/2020 | Paris, France

For 2 years, I worked as a lead developer in the Parking team, a great group of specialists with diverse cultures and expertise. We'd facilitated a lot of new cool features, upgraded our system to new modules, and improved the deployment process, successfully delivered products on production. Through code review, refactoring architecture, regular release process, maintenance of deliveries, I've gained a lot of practical experience in Agile approach, Git flow and got to be proficient in the best practices using Node.js, Python, Typescript, frontend development, OAuth, SSO, Security, DB management and Microservice architecture.

Digisec Media Ltd

Frontend Developer

05/2014 - 11/2018

- Created a new brand www.richmeetbeautiful.com Frontend by Angular5, and its Mobile App by Ionic 1.
- Creating a new brand www.victoriamilancasino.com Frontend by Angular6 and React/Redux.
- Updated the dating projects www.victoriamilan.com and www.nextlove.com to version 4.0 by Angular5.
- Created the Mobile Apps of Dating projects using ionic.
 Technologies: PHP Laravel and Symfony, Nginx, Elastic
 Search, MySql, Angular5, React/Redux, ionic, Cordova, MQTT, SCSS,
- |ira, Git

INTERESTS

Software Architecture (Microservice architecture, DDD, TDD, BDD approach)

DevOps (Kubernetes, Terraform, Ansible, CI/CD automation)

Al (Machine Learning, Deep Learning)

Soccer

Tennis